regence.com 2004-12-04

# The Regence Group Privacy Policy

**TERMS OF USE**

BY USING THIS WEB SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR AGREEMENT WITH THE FOLLOWING TERMS OF USE, SO PLEASE READ THEM CAREFULLY.  

**Acceptance of Terms.** This Regence web site (this "Site") is provided subject to the terms and conditions set forth below (the "Terms"), in addition to, and not in limitation of, the provisions of any other agreement you may enter into with Regence.

Regence may modify these Terms from time to time and without notice, effective immediately upon posting on this Site. Your continued access or use of this Site shall constitute acceptance of such modifications of the Terms. Regence has the right to terminate your access or use of this Site at any time without notice.

**Benefit Information.** No content on this Site is intended to replace or amend language for coverage that you may have with Regence. You should always consult your benefit brochure and contract for details about what your health plan covers.

**No Medical Advice.** This Site does not provide medical advice and neither the information available on this Site nor any e-mail responses to your questions shall create a physician-patient relationship or constitute the practice of medicine. The information available on this Site and from any linked sites should not be used as a substitute or supplement for professional medical advice. If you have medical or health related questions, contact your physician.

**User Obligations.** You may not use this Site in any manner that may: adversely affect this Site's resources or the availability of this Site to others; violate any local, state, national or international law; delete or revise any content on this Site; or, use this Site to harass any other person or to collect or store personal information about other visitors. If you have a unique user identifier and/or password to access secure areas, you are responsible for protecting the identifier and/or password and for any unauthorized use by others, with or without your permission.

Some parts of this Site may allow you to post, or to e-mail to Regence, materials or information ("Visitor Content"); or to access or use Visitor Content posted or e-mailed by other visitors to this Site. You grant Regence the unrestricted right to use or distribute, free of charge, any Visitor Content posted on this Site by you. You may not submit or post any material or information which is illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, or infringing of proprietary rights of any person or entity, or which contains software viruses, corrupted data, cancel bots, commercial solicitations, or mass mailings or any form of "spam." You may not use a false e-mail address to impersonate any person or otherwise mislead as to the origin of any material or information you submit or post.

Regence may review, remove or edit any Visitor Content at its discretion. Regence has no responsibility and assumes no liability for Visitor Content posted by you or by any other party.

You are responsible for all software and equipment necessary to access and use this Site, including all related expenses. In addition, you are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any password or other security measure you use in connection with this Site, and agree to notify Regence immediately of any unauthorized use of your password or other security measure.

**Privacy and Security.** Regence manages and protects your personal information in accordance with applicable laws and established company security standards and practices. For more information about privacy and security, please visit our Online Privacy and Security Statement; or, for more information about how Regence generally manages your personal information, please visit our Privacy Notice.

**No Warranty.** Regence does not warrant that any Regence Content, Visitor Content or any other content posted on this Site is accurate, complete, reliable, current or error-free. Regence does not warrant this Site will meet your requirements, or that your access or use of this Site will be uninterrupted, timely, secure or error-free, nor does Regence make any warranty whatsoever regarding the quality of any products, services, information or any other material you obtain through this Site.

**Limitation of Liability.** Regence is not responsible for any cost or damage arising directly or indirectly from your use of or inability to use this Site or any content, or the interception of loss of any data transmitted to or from this Site. Regence shall have no liability whatsoever for failure of electronic or mechanical equipment or communication, telephone or other connection problems, computer viruses, unauthorized access or interception of data or this Site, theft, or errors. Your use of this Site, and the submission of any information by you, is at your own risk.

**Copyright.** All text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data compilations, indexes, desktop tools, software and any other material or information used in connection with this Site (the Regence "Content"); the selection, arrangement, and presentation of all Regence Content (including information in the public domain); and the overall design of this Site are the property of Regence and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. Regence grants you a personal, non-transferable, non-exclusive limited license to access this Site and to download and print a single copy of Regence Content from this Site solely for: (a) your personal, non-commercial use, and provided that you do not delete or modify any copyright or other proprietary notices therefrom; or (b) as expressly permitted under any Agreement currently in effect between you and Regence. Any other copying, use, distribution or modification of Regence Content or any other property of Regence, whether in electronic or hard copy form, is strictly prohibited without the express prior written permission of Regence.

**Trademarks.** Regence and any other names of Regence or its web sites, publications, products, content or services referenced on this Site are the exclusive trademarks or service marks of Regence, including without limitation the "look and feel" of this Site and the color combinations, layout and other graphical elements of this Site. You may not use Regence's trademarks in any manner without the express, written permission of Regence. Other product and company names that appear on this Site may be subject to trademark or other rights of other parties.

**Linking to Other Web Sites.** Regence has no control over other Web sites or other resources accessed through links on this Site. Any such links are provided for your convenience only, and do not constitute an endorsement of the linked site(s) or content by Regence. Regence makes no guarantees and disclaims any implied representations or warranties about the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, completeness, or appropriateness of these sites, the information contained in them or the products or services they provide. Regence shall not be liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss incurred by you in connection with web sites or resources accessed through links on this Site.

**Linking to and Framing of this Web Site.** You may not frame any Regence Content, or use any trademark, logo or other proprietary information on this Site, without Regence's express written consent. You may not use Regence's name or trademarks in any meta-tags or other hidden text without the express written consent of Regence. You may link to this Site for non-commercial purposes only. Regence reserves the right to demand you remove any such link at any time, for any or no reason, and at Regence's sole discretion.

**Compliance with COPPA.** This Site is not directed at children under the age of 13. Regence complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and does not knowingly permit registration or submission of personally identifiable information by anyone under 13 years of age.

**Governing Law and Disputes.** These Terms, and any dispute that may arise between you and Regence, will be governed by the laws of the State of Oregon without regard to conflict of laws principles. The Terms, as may be amended from time to time, set forth the entire understanding between you and Regence as to the subject matter of the Terms, unless otherwise specifically provided under a written agreement, and supercede any prior agreements between you and Regence, whether oral or written, as to the subject matter of the Terms. Jurisdiction and venue will be in the courts of Multnomah County, Oregon for any disputes arising out of or relating to these Terms.

**Miscellaneous.** If any provision of the Terms is found to be invalid or unenforceable, the remainder of the Terms shall remain in full force and effect, and all Terms shall be enforced to the fullest extent permitted by law. No waiver or failure to assert any provision of the Terms shall be valid unless in writing and signed by an officer of Regence. Regence may assign its rights and duties under the Terms to any party, at any time, without notice. Regence reserves all rights not expressly granted in these Terms.

**The Regence Group is an independent corporation operating under a license from the Blue Cross and Blue Shield Association, an association of independent Blue Cross and Blue Shield Plans (the "Association"), permitting Regence and its affiliated health plans to use the Blue Cross and/or Blue Shield service marks in their respective service areas. The Regence Group is not an agent of the Association.**

* * *

**ONLINE PRIVACY AND SECURITY**

At Regence, protecting your personal information is important to us. Whether you are a current customer or just visiting this Site, we are as committed to protecting the information you provide through this Web site as when you provide it to us over the phone, in person or through the mail. However, we recognize, and want you to recognize, that while electronic communications have many benefits, they are not as secure as other means of communication. Please read the following information carefully to better understand how using this Site affects your privacy.

**Security Practices.**  
Regence attempts to protect online information according to applicable laws and established company security standards and practices. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under our control, and we continually evaluate new technologies for safeguarding your information. However, we cannot guarantee the confidentiality or security of electronic transmissions via the Internet because they may potentially use unsecure computers and links, and data may be lost or intercepted by unauthorized parties during such transmission. If you wish to submit personal or confidential information by a more secure means of communication, please contact us.

Sensitive information you provide to us online is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. SSL is the leading security protocol for data transfer on the Internet. This technology scrambles your account information as it moves between your PC's browser and Regence's computer systems. When information is scrambled, or encrypted in this way, it becomes nearly impossible for anyone other than Regence to read it. This secure session helps protect the safety and confidentiality of your information when you interact with Regence online.

**Cookies.**  
A cookie is a small text file that the Regence system sends to your computer to collect information about your activities on this Site, or to make it possible for you to purchase products or services from this Site and to track such purchases. The cookie transmits this information back to this Site each time your browser requests a page from this Site, and the information is stored to help facilitate your use of this Site the next time you visit. In addition to information you provide, Regence may use cookies or other passive means to collect general information such as: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the IP address of the computer you are using; the browser and operating system you are using; the date and time you access this Site; and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to this Site.

Regence uses cookies so you won't have to reenter information each time you visit this Site. If you do not want to receive cookies from this Site, you can set your browser to not accept cookies.

**Use of E-Mail.**  
Please use your own best judgment when sending information via the Internet to an e-mail address. E-mail sent via the Internet may pass through private and public networks with varying levels of security. Some networks may have taken steps to secure e-mail transmissions while others have not, thereby compromising the privacy and integrity of an e-mail. An e-mail may be copied, altered or destroyed. Regence will respect your request not to be contacted by e-mail.

Once your e-mail is received, Regence preserves the content of your e-mail, your e-mail address and our response so we can efficiently respond to questions you might have. We also do this in an effort to meet legal and regulatory requirements.

**Updates to the Statement.**  
Evolving technology will continue to provide Regence with new and better ways to safeguard your information. We may update this statement in the future to reflect these technological advances, and we encourage you to return to this page from time to time for any updates.

* * *

**NOTICE OF PRIVACY PRACTICES**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. The purpose of this is to inform you of the types of personal information we obtain and how we protect that information.

View the Notice of Privacy Practices for [Regence BlueShield of Idaho](http://www.id.regence.com/privacy/index.html), [Regence BlueCross BlueShield of Oregon](http://www.or.regence.com/docs/notice/privacyNotice.pdf), [Regence BlueCross BlueShield of Utah](http://www.ut.regence.com/privacy/index.html), or [Regence BlueShield](http://www.wa.regence.com/member/notice/docs/consumerPrivacy.pdf).

Note: To view and print the PDF document(s) listed on this page, you must have the Adobe® Acrobat® Reader installed. Get more information and/or download the free [Adobe Acrobat Reader](http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep2.html). For help with printing and working with PDF files, visit our PDF File Help page.
